http://newbreedmarketing.com/privacy

Search
Created with Sketch.
Search
Created with Sketch.
New Breed Privacy Policy
What information we collect and how we'll use it.
What Information We Collect and How We Use It
Any information we collect on our Site generally falls into the Personally Identifiable Information category. Personally Identifiable Information: This refers to information that lets us know specifically who you are. In general, you can visit our Site without telling us who you are or revealing any Personally Identifiable Information
Sharing Your Information
Except as disclosed in this Privacy Statement, we do not sell, trade, rent, or otherwise retransmit any Personally Identifiable Information we collect online unless we have your permission. Any Personally Identifiable Information you provide to us will be used for your purchases and retained in hard copy form of the original invoice as well as within our database system, which generates our invoices. From time to time, we may be required to provide Personally Identifiable Information in response to court order, subpoena, or government investigation. We also reserve the right to report to law enforcement agencies any activities that we in good faith believe to be unlawful. We may release Personally Identifiable Information when we believe that such release is reasonably necessary to enforce or apply our Limited Warranty or to protect the rights, property, and safety of others and ourselves.
Links To Other Web Sites
Links to third-party Web sites may be provided solely for your information and convenience, or to provide additional information for various other goods and services. If you use these links, you will leave our Site. This Privacy Statement does not cover the information practices of those Web sites linked to our Site, nor do we control their content or privacy policies. We suggest that you carefully review the privacy policies of each site you visit.
Changes To This Statement
Any updates or changes to the terms of this Privacy Statement will be posted here on our Site and the date of the newest version posted below. Please check back frequently, especially before you submit any Personally Identifiable Information at our Site, to see if this Privacy Statement has changed. By using our Site, you acknowledge acceptance of this Privacy Statement in effect at the time of use.
Start Building Your Growth Plan With Our Most Helpful Content
Guide
The Ultimate Guide to Inbound Marketing
Learn all the steps to take to build a successful, optimized inbound marketing strategy. Do ...
Download Now
eBook
The 30 Greatest Lead Generation Tips, Tricks and Ideas
Generating leads — both high in quantity and quality — is a marketers most important ...
Download Now
Template
Marketing Goals Calculator Template
Use this template as a tool to lay out the high level goals, and then work with your marketing ...
Download Now
Guide
The Definitive Guide to SaaS Marketing
In this guide, you will be guided through a number of comprehensive and actionable ways the ...
Download Now
Guide
The Complete Guide to Inbound Sales
The time has come to transform the way you sell. Consumers' buying habits have shifted ...
Download Now
Checklist
SEO Website Redesign Checklist
Redesigning your website? Consult this checklist to ensure your new site is configured for SEO ...
Download Now
Guide
The Essential Guide to Demand Generation
This guide will walk you through the essential fundamentals of demand generation and give you ...
Download Now
Webinar
Demand Generation Fundamentals to Scale Your Business
New Breed and G2 Crowd discuss a comprehensive look into what it takes to be a demand ...
Watch Recording
eBook
Scaling with Social
Having a social media presence is an essential part of any B2B company's online presence. ...
Download Now
Checklist
The Ten Essentials of Account-Based Marketing Checklist
There are a lot of moving pieces that go into a successful Account-Based Marketing (ABM) ...
Download Now
Guide
Your Guide to Mastering Product-Led Growth
we believe a product should speak for itself. Building a go-to-market strategy around this ...
Download Now
Checklist
The Ultimate Paid Search Checklist
Discover tips and tactics to develop and manage pay-per-click ads that will ultimately drive ...
Download Now
Guide
Brand Workshop Cheat Sheet
A cohesive brand identity aligns your messaging, provides structure to your content and helps ...
Download Now
Guide
Customer Service, Support, Success and Experience: The Guide
Understanding how to foster excellent customer relationships can contribute to your ...
Download Now
Template
Software Evaluation Worksheet
This worksheet will help you decide if a software is right for your team's needs and your ...
Download Now
Template
Marketing Budget Template
This template will help you categorize your expenses, plan your budget and track your spending ...
Download Now
Webinar
How to Plan for Q4 so that Marketing, Sales and Service Finish Off Strong
Learn how to plan for a successful Q4 with elements like budget, hiring, goals and reporting ...
Copyright © 2020 New Breed.
Created with Sketch.
HubSpot Partner
Created with Sketch.
Salesforce Partner
Created with Sketch.
AdWords Partner
Created with Sketch.
InsightSquared Partner
Privacy PolicySite Map
